<Namespace Name="System.Diagnostics">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="ef6aeaebe2981ce7e1b191a089dab9ae242e488a" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="zh-CN" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="05/10/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30734991" />
  </Metadata>
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-101">
        <see cref="N:System.Diagnostics" /> 命名空间提供类，使您能够与系统进程、事件日志和性能计数器进行交互。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="eb2ec-101">The <see cref="N:System.Diagnostics" /> namespace provides classes that allow you to interact with system processes, event logs, and performance counters.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-102"><xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog>组件提供了功能将写入到事件日志、 读取事件日志条目和创建和删除事件日志和网络上的事件源。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-102">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLog> component provides functionality to write to event logs, read event log entries, and create and delete event logs and event sources on the network.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-103"><xref:System.Diagnostics.EntryWrittenEventHandler>使您能够以异步方式与事件日志进行交互。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-103">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.EntryWrittenEventHandler> provides a way to interact with event logs asynchronously.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-104">支持的类提供访问更细致的控制，包括： 权限限制，指定事件日志类型 （控件的一个事件日志条目写入的默认数据类型），并循环访问集合的事件日志的能力条目。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-104">Supporting classes provide access to more detailed control, including: permission restrictions, the ability to specify event log types (which controls the type of default data that is written with an event log entry), and iterate through collections of event log entries.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-105">有关这些任务的详细信息，请参阅<xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogPermission>， <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType>，和<xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryCollection>类。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-105">For more information about these tasks, see the <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogPermission>, <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryType>, and <xref:System.Diagnostics.EventLogEntryCollection> classes.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-106"><xref:System.Diagnostics.Process>类提供功能，能够跨网络，监视系统进程，还可以启动和停止本地系统进程。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-106">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process> class provides functionality to monitor system processes across the network, and to start and stop local system processes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-107">除了检索正在运行的进程 （通过指定对计算机、 进程名称或进程 id） 或查看有关当前具有到处理器的访问权限的进程信息的列表，你可以获取进程线程的详细的知识和模块这两个通过<xref:System.Diagnostics.Process>类本身，并通过与之交互<xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread>和<xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessModule>类。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-107">In addition to retrieving lists of running processes (by specifying either the computer, the process name, or the process id) or viewing information about the process that currently has access to the processor, you can get detailed knowledge of process threads and modules both through the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Process> class itself, and by interacting with the <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessThread> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessModule> classes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-108"><xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessStartInfo>类，可指定各种用来启动一个新进程，例如输入、 输出和错误流、 工作目录和命令行谓词和参数的元素。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-108">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.ProcessStartInfo> class enables you to specify a variety of elements with which to start a new process, such as input, output, and error streams, working directories, and command line verbs and arguments.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-109">它们使您能够很好的控制你的进程的行为。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-109">These give you fine control over the behavior of your processes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-110">其他相关的类，你可以指定窗口样式、 进程和线程优先级以及与线程和模块的集合交互。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-110">Other related classes let you specify window styles, process and thread priorities, and interact with collections of threads and modules.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-111"><xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter>类使你能够监视系统性能时<xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory>类提供了如何创建新的自定义计数器和类别。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-111">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> class enables you to monitor system performance, while the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounterCategory> class provides a way to create new custom counters and categories.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-112">可以将写入到本地的自定义计数器以及从本地和远程计数器 （系统，以及自定义） 进行读取。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-112">You can write to local custom counters and read from both local and remote counters (system as well as custom).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-113">您可以从示例使用的计数器<xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter>类，并计算结果从使用连续的性能计数器样本<xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterSample>类。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-113">You can sample counters using the <xref:System.Diagnostics.PerformanceCounter> class, and calculate results from successive performance counter samples using the <xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterSample> class.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-114"><xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationData>类使你能够创建多个计数器的类别中，并指定其类型。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-114">The <xref:System.Diagnostics.CounterCreationData> class enables you to create multiple counters in a category and specify their types.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-115">使用性能计数器组件关联的其他类提供对计数器、 计数器权限和计数器类型集合的访问。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-115">Other classes associated with the performance counter component provide access to collections of counters, counter permission, and counter types.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-116"><xref:System.Diagnostics>命名空间还提供了允许您调试应用程序和跟踪你代码的执行的类。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-116">The <xref:System.Diagnostics> namespace also provides classes that allow you to debug your application and to trace the execution of your code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="eb2ec-117">有关更多信息，请参见 <xref:System.Diagnostics.Trace> 和 <xref:System.Diagnostics.Debug> 类。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="eb2ec-117">For more information, see the <xref:System.Diagnostics.Trace> and <xref:System.Diagnostics.Debug> classes.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>