<Namespace Name="System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="b482f98a5c4316a191cd9beb8d2d226874520920" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="434f60616a9793fa8436744549fc856e94f7a648" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="zh-CN" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="08/24/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30735491" />
  </Metadata>
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="3fdbb-101">
        <see cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection" /> 命名空间对采用应用程序扩展保护的身份验证提供支持。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="3fdbb-101">The <see cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection" /> namespace provides support for authentication using extended protection for applications.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="3fdbb-102">设计的集成 Windows 身份验证 (IWA) 使某些凭据质询响应变得通用，这意味着可以重新使用或转接。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="3fdbb-102">The design of Integrated Windows Authentication (IWA) allows for some credential challenge responses to be universal, meaning they can be re-used or forwarded.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="3fdbb-103">如果不需要此特殊设计功能然后的质询响应应为构造，最小值，目标的特定信息并，充其量，还一些通道特定信息。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="3fdbb-103">If this particular design feature is not needed then the challenge responses should be constructed with, at minimum, target specific information and, at best, also some channel specific information.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="3fdbb-104">然后，服务可以提供扩展的保护，以确保凭据质询响应包含服务特定信息 （服务提供程序名称或 SPN） 以及，如有必要，通道特定信息 （通道绑定令牌或 CBT）。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="3fdbb-104">Services can then provide extended protection to ensure that credential challenge responses contain service specific information (a Service Provider Name or SPN) and, if necessary, channel specific information (a channel binding token or CBT).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="3fdbb-105">使用此凭据交换中的信息，服务就能更好地防范恶意使用可能未正确获得的凭据质询响应。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="3fdbb-105">With this information in the credential exchanges, services are able to better protect against malicious use of credential challenge responses that might have been improperly obtained.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="T:System.Net.TransportContext" />
    <altmember cref="N:System.Security.Authentication.ExtendedProtection.Configuration" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>