<Namespace Name="System.Net.PeerToPeer">
  <Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="f73b4-101"><see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /> 命名空间提供了对等网络功能的访问权。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-101">The <see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /> namespace provides access to peer networking functionality.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-102">对等方如何彼此发现，以及如何解析标识符非常复杂，暂时的连接性以及缺少的权限对地址记录如域名系统 (DNS) 的访问。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-102">How peers discover each other and resolve identifiers is complicated by transient connectivity and the lack of access to address records such as the Domain Name System (DNS).</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-103">Windows 对等基础结构可解决此问题的调用 PNRP 的名称解析和对等方发现方案。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-103">The Windows Peer-to-Peer Infrastructure solves this problem with a name resolution and peer discovery scheme called PNRP.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-104">对等名称解析协议 (PNRP) 提供对等网络的名称解析的机制。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-104">Peer Name Resolution Protocol (PNRP) provides a name resolution mechanism for peer-to-peer networks.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-105">PNRP 旨在将名称解析为网络<xref:System.Net.IPEndPoint>完全对等的方式。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-105">PNRP is designed to resolve a name to a network <xref:System.Net.IPEndPoint> in a completely peer-to-peer manner.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-106">中提供了基本 PNRP 功能<xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer>命名空间类。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-106">Basic PNRP functionality is provided in the <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer> namespace classes.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-107">它们提供的功能创建对等方并将其在注册<xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Cloud>的对等节点。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-107">They provide the ability to create a peer and register it in a <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Cloud> of peers.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-108">它们还提供了解决功能<xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.PeerName>到其网络终结点、 TCP 端口，云或其他地址标识符。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-108">They also provide the ability to resolve a <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.PeerName> to its network endpoint, TCP port, cloud, or other address identifier(s).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-109">中提供了高级的功能的对等网络<xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration>命名空间。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-109">Advanced functionality for peer-to-peer networking is provided in the <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration> namespace.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-110">在 Windows Vista 中，PNRP 作为应用程序通过按需启动的服务提供。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-110">In Windows Vista, PNRP ships as a service that is started on demand by applications.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-111">此外，是一种 PNRP 计算机注册服务，还可以手动启用应用程序或用户如果他们想要发布的远程连接或通信的计算机名称。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-111">In addition, there is a PNRP machine registration service that can be manually enabled by applications or users if they want to publish machine names for remote connections and communications.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-112">PNRP 版本 1 包含 Windows XP Service Pack 2 (SP2)、 Windows XP Professional x64 Edition 和 Windows XP Service Pack 1 (SP1) 和高级网络包适用于 Windows XP 中。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-112">PNRP version 1 was included in Windows XP Service Pack 2 (SP2), Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, and Windows XP with Service Pack 1 (SP1) and the Advanced Networking Pack for Windows XP.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f73b4-113">此外，没有可以手动启用应用程序/用户如果没有发布的计算机名称，以进行远程连接和通信感兴趣的 PNRP 机注册服务。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f73b4-113">In addition, there is a PNRP machine registration service which can be manually enabled by applications/users if there is interest in publishing machine names for remote connection and communication.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>