<Namespace Name="System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="6013430b7450cef3a6b5d7c6e6184723336e87b3" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="16d2d159872fd213cae4b8f371d7ae9c8b027c89" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="zh-CN" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="11/17/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="51929913" />
  </Metadata>
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="1e630-101">
        <see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels" /> 命名空间包含支持并处理信道和信道接收器的类，这些信道和信道接收器在客户端调用远程对象上的方法时用作传输媒体。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="1e630-101">The <see cref="N:System.Runtime.Remoting.Channels" /> namespace contains classes that support and handle channels and channel sinks, which are used as the transport medium when a client calls a method on a remote object.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="1e630-102">信道是跨越远程处理边界（无论是在应用程序域、进程还是计算机之间）在应用程序之间传递消息的对象。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="1e630-102">Channels are objects that transport messages between applications across remoting boundaries, whether between application domains, processes, or computers.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="1e630-103">信道可以在终结点侦听入站消息，向其他终结点发送出站消息，或者进行这两种操作。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="1e630-103">A channel can listen on an endpoint for inbound messages, send outbound messages to another endpoint, or both.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="1e630-104">这使您可以插入范围广泛的协议（即使公共语言运行库不在该信道的另一端）。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="1e630-104">This enables you to plug in a wide range of protocols, even if the common language runtime is not at the other end of the channel.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="1e630-105">通道发送每个对象在发送前或接收消息之后的信道接收器对象链。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="1e630-105">Channels send each object along a chain of channel sink objects prior to sending or after receiving a message.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="1e630-106">此接收器链包含所需的基本信道功能，例如，传输或堆栈生成器接收器的接收器，但是可以自定义信道接收器链以执行特殊任务与消息或流。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="1e630-106">This sink chain contains sinks required for basic channel functionality, such as transport or stack builder sinks, but you can customize the channel sink chain to perform special tasks with a message or a stream.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="1e630-107">每个链中的每个接收器接收对象、 执行特定操作，并将其传递到下一个接收器链中。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="1e630-107">Each sink in each chain receives the object, performs a specific operation, and passes it on to the next sink in the chain.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="1e630-108">不存在规则的确切对象收到的消息接收器必须传递到下一个接收器，尽管这通常是这种情况。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="1e630-108">There is no rule that the exact object received by a message sink must be passed on to the next sink, though this will often be the case.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="1e630-109">有关详细信息，请参阅[通道](https://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6e9b60e0-9bc0-47b4-a8ef-3b78585f9a18)并[接收器和接收器链](https://msdn.microsoft.com/library/516aaab7-5b3d-4c72-83dd-d435c01af8f6)。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="1e630-109">For more information, see [Channels](https://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6e9b60e0-9bc0-47b4-a8ef-3b78585f9a18) and [Sinks and Sink Chains](https://msdn.microsoft.com/library/516aaab7-5b3d-4c72-83dd-d435c01af8f6).</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>