<Namespace Name="System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="fefc91ccc5056e6a3e0640141b2ea2b1dffd83da" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="zh-CN" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="05/10/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30734721" />
  </Metadata>
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="49794-101">
        <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> 命名空间提供了统一的访问和用户操作、计算机和组安全原则（在多个主要存储）：活动目录域服务 (AD DS)、 活动目录轻量级目录服务 (AD LDS）和机器 SAM （MSAM）。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="49794-101">The <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> namespace provides uniform access and manipulation of user, computer, and group security principals across the multiple principal stores: Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM).</span>
      </span>
      <span data-ttu-id="49794-102">
        <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> 管理独立于 <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /> 命名空间的目录对象。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="49794-102">
          <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement" /> manages directory objects independent of the <see cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" /> namespace.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="49794-103">管理的目录服务应用程序可以充分利用<xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement>API 来简化管理用户、 计算机和组主体。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-103">Managed directory services applications can take advantage of the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API to simplify management of user, computer and group principals.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="49794-104">以前需要执行的应用商店或较长的代码，例如查找用户所属的所有组的复杂知识的解决方案中的代码的几行完成<xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement>API。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-104">Solutions that previously required intricate knowledge of the store or lengthy code, such as finding all groups to which a user belongs, are accomplished in a few lines of code with the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="49794-105">以下功能都位于<xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement>API:</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-105">The following features are available on the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement> API:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="49794-106">基本目录操作，如创建和更新安全主体进行了简化。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-106">Basic directory operations such as creating and updating security principals is simplified.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="49794-107">应用程序需要较少方面的基础存储区中，若要执行这些操作知识。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-107">The application requires less knowledge of the underlying stores to perform these operations.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="49794-108">应用程序可以扩展对象模型，以便包括新类型的目录对象。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-108">Applications can extend the object model to include new types of directory objects.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="49794-109">帐户管理任务，例如启用和禁用的用户帐户，而得到简化。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-109">Account management tasks, such as enabling and disabling a user account, are simplified.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="49794-110">跨应用商店支持允许在 Active Directory 域服务 (AD DS)、 Active Directory 轻型目录服务 (AD LDS) 和机器 SAM (MSAM) 数据库，以包含来自不同类型的存储的成员的组对象。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-110">Cross-store support allows group objects in the Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS), Active Directory Lightweight Directory Services (AD LDS), and Machine SAM (MSAM) databases to contain members from different types of stores.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="49794-111">查询通过示例搜索，可在上找到<xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher>类，使应用程序能够在主体对象上设置属性和其他包含的对象匹配的属性值所选的应用商店中搜索。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-111">Query by example searching, available on the <xref:System.DirectoryServices.AccountManagement.PrincipalSearcher> class, enables applications to set properties on a principal object and search the selected store for other objects that contain matching property values.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="49794-112">计算机、 用户和组主体对象上的增强的搜索使应用程序可以搜索匹配的主体对象所选的商店。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-112">Enhanced search on computer, user and group principal objects enables applications to search the selected store for matching principal objects.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="49794-113">递归搜索，可用组主体对象，使应用程序组以递归方式搜索和返回仅是叶节点的主体对象。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-113">Recursive search, available on the group principal object, enables applications to search a group recursively and return only principal objects that are leaf nodes.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="49794-114">简化对机 SAM、 AD DS 和 AD LS 存储的凭据验证。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-114">Credential validation against the Machine SAM, AD DS, and AD LS stores is simplified.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="49794-115">通过使用快速并发绑定 （前端总线） 功能可用时提高连接速度。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-115">Connections speeds are increased by using the Fast Concurrent Bind (FSB) feature when available.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="49794-116">连接缓存减少了使用的端口数。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="49794-116">Connection caching decreases the number of ports used.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="N:System.DirectoryServices" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>