<Namespace Name="System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration">
  <Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="0132a-101"><see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration" /> 命名空间不仅增强了 <see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /> 网络功能，还提供了无服务器托管的协作会话功能。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0132a-101">The <see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration" /> namespace enhances <see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /> networking functionality and provides capabilities for serverless managed collaboration sessions.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="0132a-102">对等 (P2P) 协作基础结构以协作的活动，例如网络游戏比赛、 会议和其他交互式的多个参与者活动提供了一个对等基于网络的框架。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0132a-102">The Peer-to-Peer (P2P) Collaboration Infrastructure provides a peer-to-peer network-based framework for collaborative activities, such as network game matchmaking, conferencing, and other interactive multi-participant activities.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0132a-103">此无服务器基础结构包括简化应用程序可以跟踪不包含服务器的对等方状态、 向参与者发送邀请，发现对等节点在同一子网，并将其过程管理联系人的 Api。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0132a-103">This serverless infrastructure includes APIs that simplify the process by which applications can track peer presence without a server, send invitations to participants, discover peers on the same subnet, and manage contacts.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="0132a-104">对等协作的本机 Api 是可用于在 32 位和 64 位版本的 Windows Vista 客户端。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0132a-104">Native Peer Collaboration APIs are available on Windows Vista clients in both 32-bit and 64-bit editions.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0132a-105">对等协作 Api 不可在 Windows Server 2008 上可用。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0132a-105">Peer Collaboration APIs are not available on Windows Server 2008.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="0132a-106">注意： 协作 Api 是从服务功能，只有当该服务模拟调用方，并且调用方是交互式用户 （而不是内置的用户）。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0132a-106">NOTE: The Collaboration APIs are functional from a service only if the service is impersonating a caller, and the caller is an interactive user (as opposed to a built-in user).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="0132a-107">不支持多个联系人管理器。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="0132a-107">Multiple Contact Managers are not supported.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>